Friends, this is ICIC labment.  Okay
friends?  Look, today it has seen a total jump of 8%.
Okay friends?  It has jumped by 8%.
You look here, today's high is
around 10 111.  It is around 2011.
Look, today's candle has become so big.  Okay
friends?  Its opening today was
₹18.95.  Today is the opening.  Okay
friends?  But yesterday's
closing was at ₹1854, this is
in ICC Lambar, okay friends, it has jumped by 8%,
so let's see why it has jumped so much,
friends, the
main reason for ICC Lambar jumping so much is that the company has
approved an interim dividend of ₹6 per share for 2025-26.  Okay friends,
this dividend will be given to the shareholders
on 12th November.  The payment will be
received on 12th November.  Ok?  It has been
approved on 23rd October and the
shareholders whose names will be there on this date will have to sell
these shares till 12th November,
due to this the 8% jump has happened
because of this.